<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Marketing Team, Author at Huddles Cafe</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/techsche/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/author/techsche/</link>
	<description>The Resto-Café you always wanted</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:36:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>How Huddles Café is Hugging Global Cuisines the Way it Should be</title>
		<link>/full-course-meal/</link>
					<comments>/full-course-meal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marketing Team]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Menu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is our world, and it is getting more global than ever before. The information age has diminished boundaries and we are much more aware of other places, their different cultures, and most importantly the food (which is our point of interest). We could see beautiful places all around the world with the internet,</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-course-meal/">How Huddles Café is Hugging Global Cuisines the Way it Should be</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fusion-fullwidth fullwidth-box fusion-builder-row-1 fusion-flex-container nonhundred-percent-fullwidth non-hundred-percent-height-scrolling" style="background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0);background-position: center center;background-repeat: no-repeat;border-width: 0px 0px 0px 0px;border-color:#e2e2e2;border-style:solid;" ><div class="fusion-builder-row fusion-row fusion-flex-align-items-flex-start" style="max-width:1248px;margin-left: calc(-4% / 2 );margin-right: calc(-4% / 2 );"><div class="fusion-layout-column fusion_builder_column fusion-builder-column-0 fusion_builder_column_1_1 1_1 fusion-flex-column"><div class="fusion-column-wrapper fusion-flex-justify-content-flex-start fusion-content-layout-column" style="background-position:left top;background-repeat:no-repeat;-webkit-background-size:cover;-moz-background-size:cover;-o-background-size:cover;background-size:cover;padding: 0px 0px 0px 0px;"><div class="fusion-text fusion-text-1"><p>This is our world, and it is getting more global than ever before. The information age has diminished boundaries and we are much more aware of other places, their different cultures, and most importantly the food (which is our point of interest). We could see beautiful places all around the world with the internet, but when it comes to food, seeing is more of torture, and our mind lingers imagining the taste of it. Those who seek to authentically taste global cuisines like the Italian, the Chinese, the Indian, the French, or the Japanese must fly to those places or need to find a restaurant or hotel in their place. The two major factors, time and money, could be a constraint depending on our circumstances to fly to those wonderful countries. But those who live in Kerala won’t necessarily need to catch an airplane. Our sole intention for opening Huddles Café is to bring the original taste of global cuisines, and not a mere replication of them. Why global cuisines? Food is a great way to touch different cultures. Every food has a part of the human soul in it. If prepared with love, we could connect to the place of its origin. Having a sumptuous full-on &#8216;Sadhya&#8217; is a feeling we wish everyone from other countries to need to try. Because in the inner core we know that our &#8216;Sadhya&#8217; represents our culture, our land, and our love. So we thought about why we could bring back some great, popular, authentic, dishes across the world back to our Kerala so that our people could feel what exactly a full course Italian meal or a Chicken Burger, or Russian salad taste like.</p>
<p><b data-stringify-type="bold">Before Huddles</b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
We had gone to many places and tasted many restaurants. Some of them are so good especially when it comes to local dishes. But what about global cuisines like beef steak, barbeque chicken, spaghetti, pizza, or even burger? We felt deeply sad that in our state, Kerala (also known as God Owns Country), we had only a few restaurants serving global cuisines that could taste true to their name. We all know food is integral to every culture. Our experience with global cuisines and our circle of great chefs eventuated the idea of forming a restaurant that could feel like a Café but had all the great dishes of the world.<br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold">Birth of Huddles in Trivandrum</b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b>We summoned our great chefs and cooks. We shook hands with our local farmers so that we could get ingredients as pure as they can get. Meat has to be the finest too. We went to the finest meat houses to deal with our proportions. We made preparations and arrangements to put quality on top of everything.</p>
<p><b data-stringify-type="bold">Full Course Meal</b></p>
<p>The ‘Appetizer- Main Dish- Dessert’ way of eating is what we call a full-course meal. Three Courses is a standard. But we can add more courses if we want. A full course meal could go with courses from three to twelve.Hors-d&#8217;oeuvres<br />
Amuse-bouche<br />
Soup<br />
Appetizer<br />
Salad<br />
Fish<br />
First main dish<br />
Palate cleanser course<br />
Second main dish<br />
Cheese plate<br />
Dessert<br />
Post-meal drinks and pastries</p>
</div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;margin-top : 0px;margin-bottom : 20px;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {padding-top : 0px !important;padding-right : 0px !important;margin-right : 1.92%;padding-bottom : 0px !important;padding-left : 0px !important;margin-left : 1.92%;}@media only screen and (max-width:1024px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}@media only screen and (max-width:640px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}</style></div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-flex-container.fusion-builder-row-1{ padding-top : 0px;margin-top : 0px;padding-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px;margin-bottom : 0px;padding-left : 0px;}</style></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-course-meal/">How Huddles Café is Hugging Global Cuisines the Way it Should be</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/full-course-meal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
