<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Food Archives - Huddles Cafe</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/food/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/category/food/</link>
	<description>The Resto-Café you always wanted</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:36:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>How Huddles Café is Hugging Global Cuisines the Way it Should be</title>
		<link>/full-course-meal/</link>
					<comments>/full-course-meal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Marketing Team]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 06:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Menu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=905</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is our world, and it is getting more global than ever before. The information age has diminished boundaries and we are much more aware of other places, their different cultures, and most importantly the food (which is our point of interest). We could see beautiful places all around the world with the internet,</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-course-meal/">How Huddles Café is Hugging Global Cuisines the Way it Should be</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fusion-fullwidth fullwidth-box fusion-builder-row-1 fusion-flex-container nonhundred-percent-fullwidth non-hundred-percent-height-scrolling" style="background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0);background-position: center center;background-repeat: no-repeat;border-width: 0px 0px 0px 0px;border-color:#e2e2e2;border-style:solid;" ><div class="fusion-builder-row fusion-row fusion-flex-align-items-flex-start" style="max-width:1248px;margin-left: calc(-4% / 2 );margin-right: calc(-4% / 2 );"><div class="fusion-layout-column fusion_builder_column fusion-builder-column-0 fusion_builder_column_1_1 1_1 fusion-flex-column"><div class="fusion-column-wrapper fusion-flex-justify-content-flex-start fusion-content-layout-column" style="background-position:left top;background-repeat:no-repeat;-webkit-background-size:cover;-moz-background-size:cover;-o-background-size:cover;background-size:cover;padding: 0px 0px 0px 0px;"><div class="fusion-text fusion-text-1"><p>This is our world, and it is getting more global than ever before. The information age has diminished boundaries and we are much more aware of other places, their different cultures, and most importantly the food (which is our point of interest). We could see beautiful places all around the world with the internet, but when it comes to food, seeing is more of torture, and our mind lingers imagining the taste of it. Those who seek to authentically taste global cuisines like the Italian, the Chinese, the Indian, the French, or the Japanese must fly to those places or need to find a restaurant or hotel in their place. The two major factors, time and money, could be a constraint depending on our circumstances to fly to those wonderful countries. But those who live in Kerala won’t necessarily need to catch an airplane. Our sole intention for opening Huddles Café is to bring the original taste of global cuisines, and not a mere replication of them. Why global cuisines? Food is a great way to touch different cultures. Every food has a part of the human soul in it. If prepared with love, we could connect to the place of its origin. Having a sumptuous full-on &#8216;Sadhya&#8217; is a feeling we wish everyone from other countries to need to try. Because in the inner core we know that our &#8216;Sadhya&#8217; represents our culture, our land, and our love. So we thought about why we could bring back some great, popular, authentic, dishes across the world back to our Kerala so that our people could feel what exactly a full course Italian meal or a Chicken Burger, or Russian salad taste like.</p>
<p><b data-stringify-type="bold">Before Huddles</b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
We had gone to many places and tasted many restaurants. Some of them are so good especially when it comes to local dishes. But what about global cuisines like beef steak, barbeque chicken, spaghetti, pizza, or even burger? We felt deeply sad that in our state, Kerala (also known as God Owns Country), we had only a few restaurants serving global cuisines that could taste true to their name. We all know food is integral to every culture. Our experience with global cuisines and our circle of great chefs eventuated the idea of forming a restaurant that could feel like a Café but had all the great dishes of the world.<br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold">Birth of Huddles in Trivandrum</b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b><br />
<b data-stringify-type="bold"></b>We summoned our great chefs and cooks. We shook hands with our local farmers so that we could get ingredients as pure as they can get. Meat has to be the finest too. We went to the finest meat houses to deal with our proportions. We made preparations and arrangements to put quality on top of everything.</p>
<p><b data-stringify-type="bold">Full Course Meal</b></p>
<p>The ‘Appetizer- Main Dish- Dessert’ way of eating is what we call a full-course meal. Three Courses is a standard. But we can add more courses if we want. A full course meal could go with courses from three to twelve.Hors-d&#8217;oeuvres<br />
Amuse-bouche<br />
Soup<br />
Appetizer<br />
Salad<br />
Fish<br />
First main dish<br />
Palate cleanser course<br />
Second main dish<br />
Cheese plate<br />
Dessert<br />
Post-meal drinks and pastries</p>
</div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;margin-top : 0px;margin-bottom : 20px;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {padding-top : 0px !important;padding-right : 0px !important;margin-right : 1.92%;padding-bottom : 0px !important;padding-left : 0px !important;margin-left : 1.92%;}@media only screen and (max-width:1024px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}@media only screen and (max-width:640px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}</style></div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-flex-container.fusion-builder-row-1{ padding-top : 0px;margin-top : 0px;padding-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px;margin-bottom : 0px;padding-left : 0px;}</style></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-course-meal/">How Huddles Café is Hugging Global Cuisines the Way it Should be</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/full-course-meal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huddles’ ‘Burgerchari’ Way of Tasting Town’s Biggest Beef Burger</title>
		<link>/huddles-burgerchari-way-of-tasting-towns-biggest-beef-burger/</link>
					<comments>/huddles-burgerchari-way-of-tasting-towns-biggest-beef-burger/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[aravindnc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 03:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Menu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=387</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We lamented, struggled, and ached long to get the taste of a real burger.  We wandered across our whole town looking for burgers that would make us move. But we couldn’t harmonize with what we have tasted. Every burger had a great appeal but was subpar to our palates. Why do all of them</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/huddles-burgerchari-way-of-tasting-towns-biggest-beef-burger/">Huddles’ ‘Burgerchari’ Way of Tasting Town’s Biggest Beef Burger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fusion-fullwidth fullwidth-box fusion-builder-row-2 fusion-flex-container nonhundred-percent-fullwidth non-hundred-percent-height-scrolling" style="background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0);background-position: center center;background-repeat: no-repeat;border-width: 0px 0px 0px 0px;border-color:#e2e2e2;border-style:solid;" ><div class="fusion-builder-row fusion-row fusion-flex-align-items-flex-start" style="max-width:1248px;margin-left: calc(-4% / 2 );margin-right: calc(-4% / 2 );"><div class="fusion-layout-column fusion_builder_column fusion-builder-column-1 fusion_builder_column_1_1 1_1 fusion-flex-column"><div class="fusion-column-wrapper fusion-flex-justify-content-flex-start fusion-content-layout-column" style="background-position:left top;background-repeat:no-repeat;-webkit-background-size:cover;-moz-background-size:cover;-o-background-size:cover;background-size:cover;padding: 0px 0px 0px 0px;"><div class="fusion-text fusion-text-2"><p>We lamented, struggled, and ached long to get the taste of a real burger.  We wandered across our whole town looking for burgers that would make us move. But we couldn’t harmonize with what we have tasted. Every burger had a great appeal but was subpar to our palates.</p>
<p>Why do all of them feel so banal? What was lacking?</p>
<p>One could say, why bother so much about two pieces of bread and the fillings in between?<br />
This is because we understand how important food is for every culture and for every society that we live in, and Burger is one of those foods everyone knows in almost every country. Burgers’ universality has a reason for it. We believe it&#8217;s because every place has its own burger. For some places, It’s cross-cultural; for some others, it&#8217;s their invention. This makes our burger quest more significant. It’s bread for our sustenance and fillings to our souls.</p>
<p>After taking a big deep breath, in that minute serenity, we realized that our quest was moving in the wrong direction. We realized that it&#8217;s not what we are meant to be.  “Why do we have to look around for that perfect burger taste? Why we can&#8217;t make perfect burgers ourselves?”</p>
<p>We believe making burgers ourselves will be the ultimate way to share the best with our fellow humans, and let them know that we know how to cook with love and that we could collectively enjoy the bliss. So our quest took a new phase- we call it the path of ‘Burgerchari’. We decided to take every burger around the world and cook it here.</p>
<p>“Everyone can cook, but love for cooking is a different league.”</p>
<p>We went out with our firm hands, sensitive palates, rich ingredients, and pure love. Thus Huddles café was born in the most vibrant city, Trivandrum, in India. Since burgers are our things, Huddles café menu has the biggest burger (The Beef Tower Burger) in the whole town, not just the biggest, but also the smoothest, the purest, the tastiest, and the eternal.</p>
<p>Our chefs at Huddles prepare every dish with the whole understanding that the people who invented it and the people who taste it, deserve the respect; That the one who chews has to establish a connection with the one who prepares. This can only come from the pure love of cooking, which we have, fortunately.</p>
<p>When you come to the South of India, to God&#8217;s own Country &#8211; Kerala, never miss the capital city of Kerala, Trivandrum    ( we love the real name “Thiruvananthapuram”). If you are visiting, we would like to meet you. Because we have the greatest burgers in town.   For natives, if you haven’t come, you are welcome. But not shy away. Sometimes great things came to those who seek them. ‘The Alchemist’ tells you don’t go far away, your destiny is beside your home.</p>
<p>“Burger existed way before Wimpy and McDonalds came to our country.  And we love ‘Vada Pav’.”</p>
<p>Art of conquering The Beef Tower Burger</p>
<p>We call it our monumental work of art.  Our chefs have created this ‘Magnifique’ Burger with an exquisite blend of ingredients and flavors.  It’s been told, that for conquering heights there should be humility and patience but for our Beef Tower Burger, it&#8217;s more than patience. To scale atop our the Beef Tower Burger is to be prepared to get melted with the pleasure of satisfying all your cravings at once.</p>
<p>“Burgercharis never gets tired taking the whole Huddles Beef Tower Burger”- Saint Huddles</p>
<p>Let us properly introduce you to our Beef Tower Burger, it would be a guide to you so that you could become a ‘burgerchari’ too.  On the top floor and the ground floor of the tower, are the bread, we call them charcoal buns. Grilled brioche black buns, if we may call them by their real names. They are made with the finest of flours, baked for a perfect period to attain the ‘brioche’ character. Finest of finest French bread that could go absolutely delicious with the beef patties.</p>
<p>Talking about patties, since it’s a tower burger, we have 5 layers of beef patties between the black buns. And yes, there is cheese. They make beef patties moist in the most phenomenal way. On the Veggie side, we have Gherkins, Onion Rings, and Lettuce to make the Tower green. Our beloved Beef Tower Burger is served with the wildest combination of one pound of fries and chicken skewers. You can also quench your thirst with two favorite beverages of your choice.</p>
<p>Huddles Beef Tower Burger package is large, astoundingly delicious, and gives serious addiction to your palates. As we know you are an admirer of creations of great proportions, having our Beef Tower Burger will get you straight away to become a Burgerchari.</p>
<p>End Note</p>
<p>All our burgers are prepared with great devotion. You could find the Classic Grilled Chicken Burger or the Flamethrower, the Fried Veggie Burger, or anything smaller than our Beef Tower Burger, equally magnificent in everything.<br />
We wish luck to our fellow humans for appreciating the goodness of food,  irrespective of how small or big a burger or anything can be. Like George Bernard Shaw said, “ There is no sincere love than the love for food”.</p>
</div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-1{width:100% !important;margin-top : 0px;margin-bottom : 20px;}.fusion-builder-column-1 > .fusion-column-wrapper {padding-top : 0px !important;padding-right : 0px !important;margin-right : 1.92%;padding-bottom : 0px !important;padding-left : 0px !important;margin-left : 1.92%;}@media only screen and (max-width:1024px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-1{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-1 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}@media only screen and (max-width:640px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-1{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-1 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}</style></div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-flex-container.fusion-builder-row-2{ padding-top : 0px;margin-top : 0px;padding-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px;margin-bottom : 0px;padding-left : 0px;}</style></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/huddles-burgerchari-way-of-tasting-towns-biggest-beef-burger/">Huddles’ ‘Burgerchari’ Way of Tasting Town’s Biggest Beef Burger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/huddles-burgerchari-way-of-tasting-towns-biggest-beef-burger/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Huddle cafe is different from others?</title>
		<link>/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/</link>
					<comments>/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[aravindnc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Burger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Continental food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Premiun cafe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Seafood restaurant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steaks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian dishes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Huddles cafe is a family-owned restaurant in Trivandrum, Kerala, with a proud history of discovering and blending dishes to gratify everyone palates. We specialize in authentic Greek, Italian, American, and Indian fare, made with the finest, organic, and home-grown ingredients – many produced by the local farmers in Kerala. We love making customers feel</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/">Why Huddle cafe is different from others?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fusion-fullwidth fullwidth-box fusion-builder-row-3 fusion-flex-container nonhundred-percent-fullwidth non-hundred-percent-height-scrolling" style="background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0);background-position: center center;background-repeat: no-repeat;border-width: 0px 0px 0px 0px;border-color:#e2e2e2;border-style:solid;" ><div class="fusion-builder-row fusion-row fusion-flex-align-items-flex-start" style="max-width:1248px;margin-left: calc(-4% / 2 );margin-right: calc(-4% / 2 );"><div class="fusion-layout-column fusion_builder_column fusion-builder-column-2 fusion_builder_column_1_1 1_1 fusion-flex-column"><div class="fusion-column-wrapper fusion-flex-justify-content-flex-start fusion-content-layout-column" style="background-position:left top;background-repeat:no-repeat;-webkit-background-size:cover;-moz-background-size:cover;-o-background-size:cover;background-size:cover;padding: 0px 0px 0px 0px;"><div class="fusion-text fusion-text-3"><p>Huddles cafe is a family-owned restaurant in Trivandrum, Kerala, with a proud history of discovering and blending dishes to gratify everyone palates. We specialize in authentic Greek, Italian, American, and Indian fare, made with the finest, organic, and home-grown ingredients – many produced by the local farmers in Kerala. We love making customers feel that they’re eating at a homely cafe, so we could keep our standards at their heart. We are one of the best burger joints restaurants in Trivandrum (see our reviews). And we offer great deals on burgers, sandwiches, pizzas, and the rest of dishes in our signature menu (over 100 dishes) with a cozy lounge to sit and savor. We also offer a variety of healthy and delicious dishes, and our friendly staff will make you feel like a family. We have also been recommended as the best place for techies, besties, and lovers. We welcome everyone to our Huddles Cafe if you’re visiting Trivandrum. For those are already living in our town, don’t hesitate as you don’t want to miss the best café in Trivandrum with an ambiance soothing as it can get.</p>
<p><strong>SURF &amp; TURF</strong></p>
<p>This is one of our main courses, Surf &amp; Turf marries beef lender loin with prawn sauce. A classic dish, it is often featured as a main course at many Australian family meet-ups. Roasted potatoes or mushrooms make a good combination with this dish. It’s a dish the whole family would enjoy. Prawns are also an excellent source of unsaturated fat which make up for most of their fat content. On the healthy side, rarely do we get a source of protein which is both low fat and low calorie. Shrimps are packed with proteins and other minerals such as vitamins A and E, phosphorous, potassium, and calcium. This makes them good for the growth of tissue and bone and supports the structure of enamel in place. They don’t place stress on blood vessels and improve cholesterol levels, unlike saturated fats which risk clotting blood.</p>
<p><strong>TOWER BURGER</strong></p>
<p>A bunch of crunchy green leaves thronged and pleaded, “Lettuce in!” Along came tomatoes and onions, picked from farms, and chopped on boards. Then, the fries asked, “Can we be on board too?” As years went by, the chefs experimented and created some of the wackiest combinations to satiate their quest for new dishes. From accidental amalgamations to tested mix-ups finding a place in the gourmet world, eateries and joints came up with their signature versions of the patty and bun servings.</p>
<p>Today, there are classic takes with a contemporary hint, and there are some completely nouveau burgers that have made the cut. But what has made them visually stand out, has been their size and height. Minced meat discs, cream-loaded cheese slices, and veggie layers stacked in harmony &#8211; our Beef Tower Burger is one of the few things in this world that won’t come around every often. If you need to ultimately satisfy your growling stomach and feel how it is to dig into a scrumptious, gigantic burger come to Huddles Café as we get to you the wildest burgers in India!</p>
</div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-2{width:100% !important;margin-top : 0px;margin-bottom : 20px;}.fusion-builder-column-2 > .fusion-column-wrapper {padding-top : 0px !important;padding-right : 0px !important;margin-right : 1.92%;padding-bottom : 0px !important;padding-left : 0px !important;margin-left : 1.92%;}@media only screen and (max-width:1024px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-2{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-2 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}@media only screen and (max-width:640px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-2{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-2 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}</style></div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-flex-container.fusion-builder-row-3{ padding-top : 0px;margin-top : 0px;padding-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px;margin-bottom : 0px;padding-left : 0px;}</style></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/">Why Huddle cafe is different from others?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Pepperoni Classic</title>
		<link>/the-pepperoni-classic/</link>
					<comments>/the-pepperoni-classic/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[aravindnc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Menu]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=160</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aliquam aliquam eget est sed vulputate. Morbi commodo turpis vel condimentum semper. Integer ut commodo eros. Vestibulum non scelerisque tortor, nec porta nulla. Duis massa justo, facilisis a diam tristique, fermentum venenatis purus. Etiam vitae imperdiet mauris, vel fringilla ipsum. Etiam finibus consectetur leo, vel tincidunt</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-pepperoni-classic/">The Pepperoni Classic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fusion-fullwidth fullwidth-box fusion-builder-row-4 fusion-flex-container nonhundred-percent-fullwidth non-hundred-percent-height-scrolling" style="background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0);background-position: center center;background-repeat: no-repeat;border-width: 0px 0px 0px 0px;border-color:#e2e2e2;border-style:solid;" ><div class="fusion-builder-row fusion-row fusion-flex-align-items-flex-start" style="max-width:calc( 1200px + 0px );margin-left: calc(-0px / 2 );margin-right: calc(-0px / 2 );"><div class="fusion-layout-column fusion_builder_column fusion-builder-column-3 fusion_builder_column_1_1 1_1 fusion-flex-column"><div class="fusion-column-wrapper fusion-flex-justify-content-flex-start fusion-content-layout-column" style="background-position:left top;background-repeat:no-repeat;-webkit-background-size:cover;-moz-background-size:cover;-o-background-size:cover;background-size:cover;padding: 0px 0px 0px 0px;"><div class="fusion-text fusion-text-4"><p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aliquam aliquam eget est sed vulputate. Morbi commodo turpis vel condimentum semper. Integer ut commodo eros. Vestibulum non scelerisque tortor, nec porta nulla. Duis massa justo, facilisis a diam tristique, fermentum venenatis purus. Etiam vitae imperdiet mauris, vel fringilla ipsum. Etiam finibus consectetur leo, vel tincidunt dolor volutpat nec.</p>
<p>Fusce condimentum, dolor id tincidunt efficitur, lorem neque malesuada eros, in vulputate eros sapien eu nulla. Duis feugiat sed nunc finibus lobortis. Sed vel vulputate sem. Suspendisse magna ex, lacinia vitae sagittis quis, fringilla sit amet libero. Ut velit nisi, ultrices sed massa in, finibus dictum risus. Vivamus auctor lacus magna, sit amet convallis risus ullamcorper eu. Donec vel maximus libero, et auctor lacus.</p>
<p>Nunc massa arcu, molestie id pharetra eu, consequat vitae orci. Morbi urna tortor, venenatis eu dui id, pulvinar sagittis ligula. Praesent ultricies eros diam, sit amet convallis tellus venenatis euismod. Vestibulum interdum sagittis ex quis bibendum. Donec non aliquam neque. Pellentesque finibus maximus ipsum, sed faucibus nibh bibendum sit amet. Praesent porta dictum felis eget lobortis. Morbi pulvinar ante at facilisis sodales. Praesent imperdiet mi nec justo malesuada tincidunt. Ut semper nisi lectus, in efficitur massa condimentum in. Nam tincidunt viverra iaculis.</p>
</div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-3{width:100% !important;margin-top : 0px;margin-bottom : 20px;}.fusion-builder-column-3 > .fusion-column-wrapper {padding-top : 0px !important;padding-right : 0px !important;margin-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px !important;padding-left : 0px !important;margin-left : 0px;}@media only screen and (max-width:1024px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-3{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-3 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 0px;margin-left : 0px;}}@media only screen and (max-width:640px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-3{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-3 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 0px;margin-left : 0px;}}</style></div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-flex-container.fusion-builder-row-4{ padding-top : 0px;margin-top : 0px;padding-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px;margin-bottom : 0px;padding-left : 0px;}</style></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-pepperoni-classic/">The Pepperoni Classic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-pepperoni-classic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
