<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Seafood restaurant Archives - Huddles Cafe</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/seafood-restaurant/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/seafood-restaurant/</link>
	<description>The Resto-Café you always wanted</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 05:32:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>Why Huddle cafe is different from others?</title>
		<link>/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/</link>
					<comments>/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[aravindnc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Burger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Continental food]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Premiun cafe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Seafood restaurant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steaks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian dishes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Huddles cafe is a family-owned restaurant in Trivandrum, Kerala, with a proud history of discovering and blending dishes to gratify everyone palates. We specialize in authentic Greek, Italian, American, and Indian fare, made with the finest, organic, and home-grown ingredients – many produced by the local farmers in Kerala. We love making customers feel</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/">Why Huddle cafe is different from others?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="fusion-fullwidth fullwidth-box fusion-builder-row-1 fusion-flex-container nonhundred-percent-fullwidth non-hundred-percent-height-scrolling" style="background-color: rgba(255,255,255,0);background-position: center center;background-repeat: no-repeat;border-width: 0px 0px 0px 0px;border-color:#e2e2e2;border-style:solid;" ><div class="fusion-builder-row fusion-row fusion-flex-align-items-flex-start" style="max-width:1248px;margin-left: calc(-4% / 2 );margin-right: calc(-4% / 2 );"><div class="fusion-layout-column fusion_builder_column fusion-builder-column-0 fusion_builder_column_1_1 1_1 fusion-flex-column"><div class="fusion-column-wrapper fusion-flex-justify-content-flex-start fusion-content-layout-column" style="background-position:left top;background-repeat:no-repeat;-webkit-background-size:cover;-moz-background-size:cover;-o-background-size:cover;background-size:cover;padding: 0px 0px 0px 0px;"><div class="fusion-text fusion-text-1"><p>Huddles cafe is a family-owned restaurant in Trivandrum, Kerala, with a proud history of discovering and blending dishes to gratify everyone palates. We specialize in authentic Greek, Italian, American, and Indian fare, made with the finest, organic, and home-grown ingredients – many produced by the local farmers in Kerala. We love making customers feel that they’re eating at a homely cafe, so we could keep our standards at their heart. We are one of the best burger joints restaurants in Trivandrum (see our reviews). And we offer great deals on burgers, sandwiches, pizzas, and the rest of dishes in our signature menu (over 100 dishes) with a cozy lounge to sit and savor. We also offer a variety of healthy and delicious dishes, and our friendly staff will make you feel like a family. We have also been recommended as the best place for techies, besties, and lovers. We welcome everyone to our Huddles Cafe if you’re visiting Trivandrum. For those are already living in our town, don’t hesitate as you don’t want to miss the best café in Trivandrum with an ambiance soothing as it can get.</p>
<p><strong>SURF &amp; TURF</strong></p>
<p>This is one of our main courses, Surf &amp; Turf marries beef lender loin with prawn sauce. A classic dish, it is often featured as a main course at many Australian family meet-ups. Roasted potatoes or mushrooms make a good combination with this dish. It’s a dish the whole family would enjoy. Prawns are also an excellent source of unsaturated fat which make up for most of their fat content. On the healthy side, rarely do we get a source of protein which is both low fat and low calorie. Shrimps are packed with proteins and other minerals such as vitamins A and E, phosphorous, potassium, and calcium. This makes them good for the growth of tissue and bone and supports the structure of enamel in place. They don’t place stress on blood vessels and improve cholesterol levels, unlike saturated fats which risk clotting blood.</p>
<p><strong>TOWER BURGER</strong></p>
<p>A bunch of crunchy green leaves thronged and pleaded, “Lettuce in!” Along came tomatoes and onions, picked from farms, and chopped on boards. Then, the fries asked, “Can we be on board too?” As years went by, the chefs experimented and created some of the wackiest combinations to satiate their quest for new dishes. From accidental amalgamations to tested mix-ups finding a place in the gourmet world, eateries and joints came up with their signature versions of the patty and bun servings.</p>
<p>Today, there are classic takes with a contemporary hint, and there are some completely nouveau burgers that have made the cut. But what has made them visually stand out, has been their size and height. Minced meat discs, cream-loaded cheese slices, and veggie layers stacked in harmony &#8211; our Beef Tower Burger is one of the few things in this world that won’t come around every often. If you need to ultimately satisfy your growling stomach and feel how it is to dig into a scrumptious, gigantic burger come to Huddles Café as we get to you the wildest burgers in India!</p>
</div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;margin-top : 0px;margin-bottom : 20px;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {padding-top : 0px !important;padding-right : 0px !important;margin-right : 1.92%;padding-bottom : 0px !important;padding-left : 0px !important;margin-left : 1.92%;}@media only screen and (max-width:1024px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}@media only screen and (max-width:640px) {.fusion-body .fusion-builder-column-0{width:100% !important;}.fusion-builder-column-0 > .fusion-column-wrapper {margin-right : 1.92%;margin-left : 1.92%;}}</style></div></div><style type="text/css">.fusion-body .fusion-flex-container.fusion-builder-row-1{ padding-top : 0px;margin-top : 0px;padding-right : 0px;padding-bottom : 0px;margin-bottom : 0px;padding-left : 0px;}</style></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/">Why Huddle cafe is different from others?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Huddles Cafe</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/why-huddle-cafe-is-different-from-others/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
